datafeedfile.com 2013-03-09

# DataFeedFile.com Privacy Policy for all users including affiliates, merchants and affiliate networks

## DataFeedFile.com Privacy Policy

DataFeedFile.com DFF respect your privacy. It is your rights to know what is being collected, used and shared by DFF while using our website and/or services. This document is DFF's Privacy Policy, this privacy policy governs the way we collect, retain and share information.

### Collection and Use of User Details

While browsing or using DFF website, its tools, its javascripts and data, we may collect and use personal details about you. DFF does collect personal and business information such as your name, address, e-mail address, company name and job title via DFF's website forms for sign-up and/or other purposes.

While you visit or browse through this website, we also collect website usage information and information about your computer and internet connection, including your computer's IP address the type and version of your internet browser and operating system you use, your internet domain and the referrer URL of the previous website if you arrived on DFF website using link from another website.

This clause also apply for our affiliates and their customers and/or visitors as our HTML code and/or javascripts and tools also collect website usage information and information about your computer and internet connection, including your computer's IP address the type and version of your internet browser and operating system you use, your internet domain and the referrer URL of the previous website if you arrived on DFF website using link from another website.

DFF use information collect for the following purposes:  
\- Internal use reporting and statistic  
\- Statistics reporting for Merchants' Affiliate Managers  
\- Send newsletter and notifications (only if you opt-in to receive them)  
\- Personalize content of advertisement, banners and text links

### Tracking and Performance Information

DFF is not an affiliate network, we do not track sales or commissions. All tracking are still done by the affiliate networks. We do not have information about your sales, commissions and/or conversion rates. 

### User Choices

The registration form(s) in DFF website provides you with a series of choices regarding promotional activity, notification methods and other communication with you.

It is the users' choice and responsibility to choose the appropriate option(s) that best suit the need of each individual user.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small file which is placed on the user's hard drive during a to DFF website. This file allows the user to move quickly and easily around our site. It is used to identify returning users and to identify affiliates and merchants. We may also use cookies and the information we collect to show you relevant content and advertising.

You can delete cookies from your hard drive at any time. Bear in mind, though, that if you delete these cookies, any settings such as your stored username and password will have to be reset when you log in again.

### E-mails

DataFeedFile.com uses both our own e-mail server and reputable third parties to deliver the e-mails you will receive from our site if you subscribe to our e-mail newsletters or have chosen to receive information about DFF products and services. These third parties use unique identifiers and invisible images (often called "pixel tags" or "clear GIFs") to perform message open sensing, message format sensing, and clickthrough sensing on behalf of DFF in order to bring you better service.

### Phone numbers

Phone numbers are collected strictly to filter out non-serious applicants and serve as clue about affiliate's location. DFF will not phone number information to contact affiliate without prior consent. DFF will never sell or share phone number information with any other company or 3rd party organization.

### Advertisements, Tools, Products and Services

DataFeedFile.com provide information, data, tools and services which relies on other reputable 3rd party companies and/or website, such as our affiliates, merchants and affiliate networks. In the process of serving advertisements, tools, products and services, DFF, its merchants and our 3rd party affiliate networks may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your computer on behalf of DFF, 3rd party affiliate network and/or merchant site in order to bring to you more relevant information and content. By using DFF advertisements, tools, products and services, affiliates and merchants has both agreed and understood that DFF has taken appropriate measures to ensure private information are not misused.

### Security Policy

DataFeedFile.com has appropriate measures in place to ensure that users' personal details are not misused, accidentally destroyed, lost or altered within our server environment.  
Occasions will arise when customer information is passed outside local server network to other data processors (i.e. fulfillment bureaus, database consultants etc.) but they will only act upon instruction from DFF in order to perform the services required.

### Transfer of Personal Data Overseas

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing DFF website and using our products and services, and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.

### Updating Customer Details

It is important to us that we have your correct contact information so that you don't miss out on further correspondence or experience problems with the delivery of products and services.

We encourage all users both affiliates and merchants to keep their contact information (e-mails, phone numbers and physical address) up to date on our server.

### Children Under 13

DataFeedFile.com does not intentionally collect any personally identifiable information from individuals under the age of 13. When necessary, underage users will be told not to submit any personal details and we will make every effort to delete any details of such users where a parent or guardian has informed us that these details have been collected.

### Changes to this policy / statement

Due to changes in legislation and best practice or enhancements to functionality and content of DataFeedFile.com and its products and services, we may make changes to our privacy policy and will reflect those changes in this statement, all users including affiliates and merchants are responsible to check this statement from time to time.
